{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which champion is known as The Bounty Hunter ?",
      "options": ["Renekton", "Miss Fortune", "Sivir", "Gankplank"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Sejuani's rival?",
      "options": ["Ashe", "Taric", "Kayle", "Tryndramere"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Runes of Clarity provide what attribute?",
      "options": [
        "Mana Regen per 5",
        "Magic Penetration",
        "Mana",
        "Ability Power"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Swain's bird named?",
      "options": ["Aerith", "Betty", "Beatrice", "Johnson"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What champion does not have a hidden passive?",
      "options": ["Zilean", "Fizz", "Tryndamere", "Diana"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is called Fox?",
      "options": ["Ashe", "Ahri", "Illaoi", "Kindred"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which champion has the passive called 'Equilibrium' ?",
      "options": ["Vayne", "Teemo", "Tryndamere", "Veigar"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What champion is categorized as both a 'support' and a 'pusher'?",
      "options": ["Nidalee", "Morgana", "Janna", "Illaoi"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Miss Fortune FRIST name?",
      "options": ["Sarah", "Lisa", "Venna", "Tina"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What champion does not reside in Freljord?",
      "options": ["Anivia", "Tryndamere", "Ashe", "Sejuani"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Miss Fortune doesn't favor....",
      "options": ["Feelings", "Fools", "Teemo", "Bushes"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Swain shares three quotes with two other champions, what quote does he share with Garen?",
      "options": [
        "Victory awaits!",
        "My Pleasure",
        "Ahghhh...",
        "If you insist"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is related to Katarina?",
      "options": ["Caitlin", "Renekton", "Zed", "Cassiopeia"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What champion is the leader of the group known as the 'Black Rose' ?",
      "options": ["Talon", "Zyra", "Katarina", "Leblanc"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which champion is known as 'The Deathsinger'?",
      "options": ["Kassadin", "Nocturne", "Karthus", "Talon"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company designed Urfrider Corki and Piltover Blitzcrank?",
      "options": ["BANK", "REEOT", "GANK", "Riot Games"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "What champion is named after Marc Merrill's wife?",
      "options": ["Ashe", "Karma", "Tristana", "Diana"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "Which champion was made for Marc Merrill?",
      "options": ["Darius", "Tryndamere", "Twisted Fate", "Malzahar"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 40
    }
  ]
}
